Guide to the Class of 1864, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1864, Yale College, records
1864-1914
RU 1028
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(2 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, meeting minutes, printed material, photographs, and clippings and reprints of writings by and about members of the Yale College Class of 1864, maintained by the class secretary, Charles G. Rockwood.
Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1864
Rockwood, Charles G. (Charles Greene), 1843-1913
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, meeting minutes, printed material, photographs, and clippings and reprints of writings by and about members of the Yale College Class of 1864, maintained by the class secretary, Charles G. Rockwood.
Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1864; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Class records, 1864-1914; Accession 19ND-A-446
  - Class secretary business, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - Conklin, Clinton, 1899, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Rockwood, Charles, 1895-1907 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Records and addresses", undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Addresses, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1865, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Printed material, circa 1867-1907 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Yale Association of Class Secretaries, 1903-1908 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni
    - Atterbury, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Burnett, Charles H., 1903 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Crissey, Theron W., 1900 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Darling, Samuel, circa 1892-1903 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Gregory, Lewis, 1897-1898 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Hoyt, James P., 1887, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Ingersoll, Charles D., 1892 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Jessup, Huntting C, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Owen, Henry, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Page, Olaf, undated, 1891, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Randall, J. F., undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Rapalje, Stewart, 1897 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Robinson, Arthur, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Rockwood, Charles, 1896-1903 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Satterhwaite, Thomas E., undated, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Sawin, Theophilus, undated, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Semple, E. H., undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Taft, Charles P., undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Teal, John W., 1881, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Van Gelder, James H., circa 1904 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Warren, Edwin F., 1877, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Watson, Beniah, 1899 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Welles, Edgar T., 1893 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Whitney, Henry M., circa 1899-1903 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Williams, Clarence R., undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Williams, Job, 1884, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Williams, Moseley H., 1887, 1897 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Woodruff, Frances E., circa 1894-1898 (Box 2, Folder 37)